conversationsnetwork.org 2013-10-06

# Privacy Policy for The Conversations Network

This page is archived for historical purposes. The Conversations Network ceased operation of its websites as of the end of 2012.

The personal privacy of Internet users is extremely important to The Conversations Network and we recognize and support the protection of visitors' privacy rights as a fundamental principle of our business.

### Information Collection and Use

The Conversations Network does not sell, share, or rent email addresses, mailing lists or any other personal information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

### Clickthroughs

In the process of delivering web pages and email, The Conversations Network recognizes any URLs that are clicked and may record some information supplied by your computer, such as the type of browser, operating system and IP address.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, optionally stored on a visitor's hard drive, containing information that is placed there by a website. This information is often used to identify successive visits by the same web browser to the same site, or to remember information between sessions on the website. The Conversations Network uses two types of cookies: First, we will save an encrypted version of your login information as a cookie on your computer. This will allow you or anyone using your computer to bypass the login process on subsequent visits. Second, we will use a temporary cookie (one that will disappear as soon as you close your browser) to make our site easier to use by remembering your preferences from one page to another.

Some of our undewriters and partners also use cookies and may track your usage patterns in ways beyond our control. For example, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. One such cookie is the [DoubleClick DART Cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) from Google. You can opt-out from the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Log Files

We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our service, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Trackers

Trackers are invisible codes on web pages or in email that have special names which permit the loading of the web page or email to be tracked by a web server. The Conversations Network uses trackers on our web site and in HTML email we send to detect when a web page is viewed or the email is opened.

### Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners. Shared aggregated information is not linked to any information about any individual person.

### Links

Our web sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that The Conversations Network is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected, and services provided, by our web site.

### Email

From time to time we may offer users the opportunity to subscribe to one of our mailing lists. If a user wishes to subscribe to a list, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We send e-mail messages only to those who have opted-in for particular purposes such as to be informed of new programs on our site.

### Unsolicited Commercial Email (UCE) Policy

The Conversations Network does not send "spam." The term "spam" refers to emailing a message to address(es) that have not asked to receive it. In addition, every message sent by The Conversations Network provides information about unsubscribing from (that is, choosing not to receive) future mailings. Every email message The Conversations Network sends contains instructions that allow you unsubscribe from our list(s). To contact The Conversations Network to request removal from future The Conversations Network email communications, you can send email to webmaster@conversationsnetwork.org specifying the address that you wish to unsubscribe, or send mail to the US postal address:

> The Conversations Network  
> c/o Internet Archive  
> 300 Funston Avenue  
> San Francisco, CA 94118 (US)  
>  or call +1 415.561.6767

### Forms and Surveys

From time to time we may request information from users via forms or surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code and profession). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving this site and our services. Users of our website are notified on the website when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

### Security

Our web sites do not collect highly sensitive information (such as credit card numbers or Social Security numbers) from our users. If you receive email requesting any such information, please report it immediately to webmaster@conversationsnetwork.org.

Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out personal information online (including, for example, using your passwords) there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While The Conversations Network strives to protect your perosnal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using our web sites, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through your use of our web sites and that any personal information, general information, or other data or information received from your through your use of our web sites is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume.Notification of Changes 

If we materially change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our web site's homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify registered users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

You can review the most current version of the Privacy Policy at any time by clicking the Privacy Policy link on The Conversations Network website. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact webmaster@conversationsnetwork.org.
